<overrides>
	<file name=".*WEB-INF/config\.xml">
		<replaceXML xpath="resources">
			<resource enabled="true">
      	<name>main-db</name>
      	<provider>jeeves.resources.dbms.JNDIPool</provider>
      	<config>
        	<context>java:/comp/env</context>
        	<resourceName>jdbc/geonetwork</resourceName>
        	<url>jdbc:oracle:thin:@aqua.hba.marine.csiro.au:1521:AQUA</url>
        	<provideDataStore>true</provideDataStore>
        	<maxOpenPreparedStatements>300</maxOpenPreparedStatements>
      	</config>
    	</resource>
		</replaceXML>
	</file>
  <!-- add ldap settings in config-security-ldap.xml -->
  <spring>
    <import file="WEB-INF/config-security-ldap.xml"/>
    <!-- add user search bean (so that we can search in more than one 
         organisational unit) and then set it on the bindAuthenticator
         bean in config-security-ldap.xml -->
    <import file="WEB-INF/config-ldap-marlin2-ldapUserSearch.xml"/>
    <set bean="bindAuthenticator" property="userSearch" ref="ldapUserSearch"/>
  </spring>
	<!-- add marlin description to the strings file -->
	<file name=".*geonetwork/loc/eng/xml/strings\.xml">
		<replaceXML xpath="welcome.text">
     <!--MarLIN Home Text-->
     <h4>Welcome to MarLIN - The Marine and Atmospheric Research Information Network</h4>

     <p>The Marine and Atmospheric Research Information Network (MarLIN) is the central, searchable repository for dataset descriptions (metadata) relating to data held by the CSIRO Division of Marine and Atmospheric Research (CMAR) in Australia. MarLIN currently contains descriptions of over 4,000 datasets held by the Division, many of which are available online via relevant hyperlinks to data files, OGC web services, or our "Data Trawler" application. Metadata records are authored either by CMAR scientists or by the Divisional Data Centre, and most are also exported to external systems including the Australian Spatial Directory (ASDD) and the metadata repository associated with the Australian Ocean Data Network (AODN), which also provides its own map-based data viewing facility for datasets originating from multiple agencies within Australia.</p>

     <p>The following links are supplied for MarLIN users:
     <ul>
     <li><b>Catalog:</b> Search MarLIN: default is to show all records, then you can narrow your search using either the free text search box supplied, or the pre-formulated filters in the left sidebar; "show advanced options" adds additional keyword options from drop down lists, together with geographic and/or temporal filters. Individual metadata records can then be viewed or opened for editing by authorised metadata owners.</li>
     <li><b>Map:</b> shows bounding boxes for all datasets in the present search results; also displays detailed polygons (from web map services) from selected datasets as available</li>
     <li><b>About:</b> Contains some background information about the present version of MarLIN</li>
     <li><b>Home:</b> takes you back to this page</li>
     </ul>
     </p>
		</replaceXML>
    <addXML xpath="">
      <about.text>
        <!--About MarLIN Text-->
        <h4>About MarLIN</h4>

        <p>This is a new (May 2014) release of the MarLIN software based on the open source <a href="http://geonetwork-opensource.org/">GeoNetwork</a> product, with enhanced metadata elements and functionality compared with the previous MarLIN system which was in use 1998-2014. Significant advances include:
        <ul>
        <li>New, internationally-compliant metadata format based on ISO 19115 (and the Australian Marine Community Profile of the same)</li>
        <li>Facility to link to OGC web services e.g. web map service (WMS) which can be used to plot data extents on the MarLIN map viewer, and also accessed via external Portals</li>
        <li>New user and group management for metadata authoring, including login with standard (nexus) credentials</li>
        <li>Shared application maintenance and development with the international GeoNetwork community and other Australian users</li>
        <li>Improved metadata sharing between multiple repositories via harvesting</li>
        <li>Enhanced thesaurus support e.g. from externally maintained vocabularies and services</li>
        <li>Extensive use of stylesheets, etc. to cover data display rather than encoding everything at source code level</li>
        <li>Updated look and feel to metadata search and edit pages including use of modern web technologies as appropriate.</li>
        </ul></p>

        <p>For more information about the GeoNetwork Open Source product on which this version of MarLIN is built, see the <a href="http://geonetwork-opensource.org/">GeoNetwork project home page</a>. To contact the MarLIN development team to request new features or report problems, please use the email <a href="mailto:CMARMarLINSupport@csiro.au">CMARMarLINSupport@csiro.au</a>.</p>
      </about.text>
    </addXML>
	</file>
	<!-- Add geoserver layers for maps in classic interface only -->
	<file name=".*WEB-INF/config-gui\.xml">
		<!-- set server to use geoserver -->
		<replaceAtt xpath="mapViewer/layers/layer" attName="server" value="http://marlin2-dev.its.csiro.au/geoserver/wms" />
		<!-- switch off OSM in html5ui etc -->
		<replaceXML xpath="map/osm_map"/>
	</file>
</overrides>
