<overrides>
	<file name=".*WEB-INF/config\.xml">
		<replaceXML xpath="resources">
			<resource enabled="true">
      	<name>main-db</name>
      	<provider>jeeves.resources.dbms.JNDIPool</provider>
      	<config>
        	<context>java:/comp/env</context>
        	<resourceName>jdbc/geonetwork</resourceName>
        	<url>jdbc:oracle:thin:@aqua.hba.marine.csiro.au:1521:AQUA</url>
        	<provideDataStore>true</provideDataStore>
        	<maxOpenPreparedStatements>300</maxOpenPreparedStatements>
      	</config>
    	</resource>
		</replaceXML>
	</file>
  <!-- add ldap settings in config-security-ldap.xml -->
  <spring>
    <import file="WEB-INF/config-security-ldap.xml"/>
    <!-- add user search bean (so that we can search in more than one 
         organisational unit) and then set it on the bindAuthenticator
         bean in config-security-ldap.xml -->
    <import file="WEB-INF/config-ldap-marlin2-ldapUserSearch.xml"/>
    <set bean="bindAuthenticator" property="userSearch" ref="ldapUserSearch"/>
  </spring>
	<!-- add marlin description to the strings file -->
	<file name=".*geonetwork/loc/eng/xml/strings\.xml">
		<replaceXML xpath="welcome.text">
     <!--Marlin Home Text-->
<h4>Welcome to Marlin - The metadata system for the CSIRO Oceans and Atmosphere Flagship</h4>
<p>Marlin is the central, searchable repository for dataset descriptions (metadata) relating to data held by the CSIRO Oceans and Atmosphere Flagship in Australia.</p>
		</replaceXML>
    <replaceXML xpath="about.text">
        <!--About MarLIN Text-->
        <h4>About Marlin</h4>
<p>Marlin is the central, searchable repository for dataset descriptions (metadata) relating to data held by the CSIRO Oceans and Atmosphere Flagship in Australia. Marlin currently contains descriptions of several thousand datasets held by this CSIRO Flagship, many of which are available online via hyperlinks to data files, OGC web services, or our "Data Trawler" application.</p>
<p>The following links are supplied for Marlin users:             
<ul>
<li><b>Catalog:</b> provides both simple free text search and keyword-based filtering (default), plus advanced options to search for metadata
</li>
<li><b>Map:</b> shows bounding boxes for all datasets in the present search results; also can add individual custom spatial extents (from web map services) for selected datasets as available, using the green "add to map" buttons
</li>
<li><b>About:</b> contains some background information about the present version of Marlin
</li>
<li><b>Home:</b> takes you back to this page.
</li>                               
<li>CSIRO and other registered users should <b>Sign In</b> via the link above the CSIRO and Marlin logo to view internal records and/or to create and edit metadata (for CSIRO users, your nexus ID and password should be used).
</li>                               
</ul>                
</p>
        <p>This is a new (May 2014) release of the Marlin software based on the open source <a href="http://geonetwork-opensource.org/">GeoNetwork</a> product, with enhanced metadata elements and functionality compared with the previous MarLIN system which was in use 1998-2014. Significant advances include:
        <ul>
        <li>New, internationally-compliant metadata format based on ISO 19115 (and the Australian Marine Community Profile of the same)</li>
        <li>Facility to link to OGC web services e.g. web map service (WMS) which can be used to plot data extents on the Marlin map viewer, and also accessed via external Portals</li>
        <li>New user and group management for metadata authoring, including login with standard (nexus) credentials</li>
        <li>Shared application maintenance and development with the international GeoNetwork community and other Australian users</li>
        <li>Improved metadata sharing between multiple repositories via harvesting</li>
        <li>Enhanced thesaurus support e.g. from externally maintained vocabularies and services</li>
        <li>Extensive use of stylesheets, etc. to cover data display rather than encoding everything at source code level</li>
        <li>Updated look and feel to metadata search and edit pages including use of modern web technologies as appropriate.</li>
        </ul></p>

        <p>For more information about the GeoNetwork Open Source product on which this version of Marlin is built, see the <a href="http://geonetwork-opensource.org/">GeoNetwork project home page</a>. To contact the Marlin development team to request new features or report problems, please use the email <a href="mailto:CMARMarLINSupport@csiro.au">CMARMarLINSupport@csiro.au</a>.</p>
    </replaceXML>
	</file>
	<!-- Add geoserver layers for maps in classic interface only -->
	<file name=".*WEB-INF/config-gui\.xml">
		<!-- set server to use geoserver -->
		<replaceAtt xpath="mapViewer/layers/layer" attName="server" value="http://marlin2-dev.its.csiro.au/geoserver/wms" />
		<!-- switch off OSM in html5ui etc -->
		<replaceXML xpath="map/osm_map"/>
	</file>
</overrides>
